Guide to the International Typographical Union Local 99 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- RECORD GROUP F: INTERNATIONAL TYPOGRAPHICAL UNION LOCAL 355 BELLINGHAM, 1951-1980 (Box-folder 63/1-65/11)
  - SERIES I: ORGANIZATION AND ELECTION MATERIALS, 1951-1974 (Box-folder 63/1, 63/24-63/25)
    - Constitution, Bylaws, Elections, 1951-1974 (Box-folder 63/1)
    - Local Union Merger Straw Vote: Statewide or Area Mergers, 1973 (Box-folder 63/24)
    - Photographs: Organization Meeting, 1971 (Box-folder 63/25)
  - SERIES II: AGREEMENTS AND CONTRACT MATERIALS, 1969-1980 (Box-folder 63/2, 63/11, 65/2, 65/9)
    - Tacoma Typographical Union No. 170 and Tacoma News Tribune Supplemental Agreement, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 63/2)
    - Contract Proposal: Wages, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 63/11)
    - Contract Files, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 65/2)
    - Newspaper Contracts, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 65/9)
  - SERIES III: CORRESPONDENCE, 1953-1974 (Box-folder 63/3, 63/8-63/10, 63/12-63/13, 63/29, 63/31, 63/33)
    - Apprentice Correspondence and Forms, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 63/3)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (1 of 2), 1953-1969 (Box-folder 63/8)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (2 of 2), 1953-1969 (Box-folder 63/9)
    - Monthly Letters and Announcements, 1958-1967 (Box-folder 63/10)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 63/12)
    - Correspondence, 1955-1964 (Box-folder 63/13)
    - Miscellaneous Communications, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 63/29)
    - National Labor Relations Act: Related Correspondence, 1957-1974 (Box-folder 63/31)
    - Miscellaneous Communications, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 63/33)
  - SERIES IV: FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1927-1974 (Box-folder 63/4, 63/27, 63/30)
    - Financial Statements, 1965-1974 (Box-folder 63/4)
    - Loan and Donation Receipts, Money Orders, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 63/27)
    - Pension Merger, 1968 (Box-folder 63/30)
  - SERIES V: COUNCIL/APPRENTICESHIP MATERIALS, NOTES, DISCUSSION, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 63/5-63/7, 63/19, 63/32)
    - Apprenticeship and Training Council (1 of 2), 1968-1972 (Box-folder 63/5)
    - Apprenticeship and Training Council (2 of 2), 1968-1972 (Box-folder 63/6)
    - Washington State Labor Council, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 63/7)
    - Notes on Seattle New Processes School, 1969 (Box-folder 63/19)
    - Discussions with the Bellingham Herald and Daily Olympian, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 63/32)
  - SERIES VI: PHOTOGRAPHS, C. 1930-1973 (Box-folder 63/14-63/63/18, 63/20-63/23, 63/26, 63/28, 65/10)
    - Candid Photographs, Washington State Typographical Conference, 1972 (Box-folder 63/14)
    - Photographs, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 63/15)
    - Mickey Neylan Retirement Photos, 1970 (Box-folder 63/16)
    - Photographs, Spokane Quick Print, c.1930 (Box-folder 63/17)
    - Photographs, Local 202 Pension Plan Decision Meeting, 1969 (Box-folder 63/18)
    - Photographs, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 63/20)
    - ITU Graphic Arts Training Center in Colorado Springs: Promotional Photographs, c.1969 (Box-folder 63/21)
    - Photographs, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 63/22)
    - Photographs, 1961-1970 (Box-folder 63/23)
    - Conference, H. Markes Stith Retirement Photographs and Notes, 1962 (Box-folder 63/26)
    - Photographs, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 63/28)
    - Photographs:(1) Picture of toddler standing by chair, AP Johnson written on back - Undated (2) Group shot of 4 men and 1 woman at ceremony, stamped on back "Joseph Perrino Photogrpaher, numbered 03086410, dated April 9, 1964, note reads "2 Col Thurs Service Noted" (Box-folder 65/10)
  - SERIES VII: MINUTES, 1925-1974 (Box-folder 64/1-64/2)
    - Minutes for Bellingham Typographical Union, 1925-1969 (Box-folder 64/1)
    - Minutes for Bellingham Typographical Union, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 64/2)
  - SERIES VIII: EVERETT MEMBERSHIP RECORDS, 1948-1956 (Box-folder 65/1)
    - Everett Membership Records, 1948-1956 (Box-folder 65/1)
  - SERIES IX: CONVENTION MATERIALS, 1960-1973 (Box-folder 65/3-65/8, 65/11)
    - Convention Materials (107th Convention of the International Typographical Union in Washington D.C.), 1965 (Box-folder 65/3)
    - Joint Apprenticeship Committee Convention Materials, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 65/4)
    - Convention Materials (108th and 109th Conventions of the International Typographical Union), 1966-1967 (Box-folder 65/5)
    - Business cards, Undated (Box-folder 65/6)
    - Laws Committee, 1964-1971 (Box-folder 65/7)
    - Convention Materials (111th Conventions of the International Typographical Union), 1969 (Box-folder 65/8)
    - Minority Percentage Sheet, assorted business cards, Working Cards/Permits, Bulletins, and notes, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 65/11)